PERSONAL INFO

(C) 054-8047997

avrikaufman@gmail.com

https://avikaufman.tech/

www.linkedin.com/in/avikaufman-b93540200

https://github.com/avikaufman

LANGUAGES AND TECHNOLOGIES

Java

Python

C #

SQL

JavaScript

HTML

CSS

Git VCS

Bash

PERSONAL SKILLS

Teamwork

Full Dedication

Pursuing Excellence

Not afraid of hard work

Proactive

Autodidact

HOBBIES

Chess

Hiking

Slackline

Avi Kaufman

A B.Sc. Student, Looking for a Student Position

I departed the Ultra-Orthodox community, independently pursued my education, earned a full "Bagrut" in two years excelling in English and math, and found my passion for math and programming.

Today, I am in the last year of my B.A. in Computer Science at Reichman University, supported by the 'Keren Or' scholarship. My journey in this program has been both challenging and rewarding, leading me to the final stages of my undergraduate studies.

Highly motivated, enthusiastic, looking for new opportunities.

EDUCATION

Present - Last year (4th Year) of a B.A. in Computer Science at Reichman University, Herzliya.

SELECTED COURSES:

Data Structures, Algorithms, Operating Systems, Advanced Programming, Machine Learning From Data, Full Stack Development

PROJECT:

Blog application with React front-end, Python REST API back-end, MySQL database, deployed on AWS (RDS & EC2)

EXTRACURRICULAR:

Pulse Healthtech Innovation Entrepreneurship Club

Volunteer Tutor for "Keren Or" scholarship, Math and Programing

2017 - External Bagroot (High School Equivalency test), Tel-Aviv

2010 - Knesset Meir Yeshiva, Rishon Le'Zion

COURSES

2022 - Intro to machine learning, Kaggle

2019 - Computer Science and Python Programing, Campus

2016 - Emergency Medical Technician (EMT) Course, MDA

EMPLOYMENT

2018 - Present - Emergency Medical Technician (EMT), IDF Disabled Veterans Organization "Beit Halochem" Tel Aviv

VOLUNTEERING

2018 - Present - "Hillel" and "Out for Change" nonprofits

NATIONAL SERVICE

2016-2017 - Emergency Medical Technician (EMT), Magen David Adom (MDA), Tel Aviv

2015-2016 - Group Leader, <u>Jordan River Village</u> camp for children living with chronic diseases, Givat Avni

2013-2014- Pre-Military "Mechinat HaEmek" program